{
    "subject": "resource/Chorus_(2015_film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/director",
    "object": "resource/Fran\u00e7ois_Delisle",
    "human_readable": "The director of the film 'Chorus' is Fran\u00e7ois Delisle.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9786087870597839,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Fran\u00e7ois Delisle."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9753028154373169,
            "question": "Fran\u00e7ois Delisle is known for directing which film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9678356647491455,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Fran\u00e7ois Delisle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9350570440292358,
            "question": "Is Fran\u00e7ois Delisle a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.886574387550354,
            "question": "Can you tell me about a film directed by Fran\u00e7ois Delisle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8358074426651001,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'Chorus'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8215122818946838,
            "question": "What film did Fran\u00e7ois Delisle direct?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.743759274482727,
            "question": "What is the name of the director of 'Chorus'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.718706488609314,
            "question": "What is the profession of Fran\u00e7ois Delisle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5401099920272827,
            "question": "Who is associated with the film 'Chorus'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The director of the film 'Chorus' is Fran\u00e7ois Delisle.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3032_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the profession of Fran\u00e7ois Delisle?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3032_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the director of 'Chorus'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3032_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What film did Fran\u00e7ois Delisle direct?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3032_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3032_136.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3032_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3032_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3032_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3032_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3032_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3032_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3032_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3032_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3032_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the answer in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information across multiple documents supports that Fran\u00e7ois Delisle is indeed the director of the film \"Chorus.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}